# **Rahul Kumar**

# Web Developer

Linkedin | Profile

Email: karnrk5@gmail.com | Phone: (+91) 9205009528,8368232719 Address: First Floor H-317 Alpha 2,Greater Noida (UP) 201308

### **PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY**

A skilled web developer with over 5 years of experience in the industry. I have successfully worked on various web projects, specializing in HubSpot (HUBL Code), HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript. I am eager to contribute my technical and management expertise to a progressive organization, drive organizational growth, and stay updated with emerging technologies.

# Areas of professional expertise:

- HubSpot(HUBL Code)
- Javascript
- Figma, Adode XD

• HTML5

- CSS3
- Bootstrap, Responsive Design
- Jquery

#### **EDUCATION**

- MCA, IGNOU (2019 to 2023)
- BCA, IGNOU (2015 to 2021)

#### **ACHIEVEMENT**

I was honored with the **Outstanding Performance Award** by Prodigitas IT Services PVT LTD for my exceptional contributions to a Global MNC Project.

# **EXPERIENCE**

- 1. Prodigitas IT Services PVT LTD, Pune (Maharashtra) Website Developer (March 2022 to Present)
  - Successfully contributed to a diverse range of client projects in a supportive and dynamic environment.
  - Expanded proficiency in HubSpot, including working on templates and email templates.
  - Explored and implemented new content management systems (CMS) such as Marketo and WebFlow.
  - Played a pivotal role in developing Marketo emails for a significant MNC project.

# 2. The Web Plant Pvt. Ltd., NEW DELHI - HubSpot Developer

(Feb 2019 to March 2022)

- Collaborated on multiple website development projects using HubSpot.
- Acquired expertise in HUBL code and various aspects of HubSpot development.

# 3. IParable, NOIDA - Web developer

- Contributed to the development of an HR portal, specializing in front-end development.
- Collaborated with the backend team utilizing PHP.
- Designed and implemented a fully responsive and user-friendly portal with multiple pages.